[
    {
      "question": "The explanation was too ______.",
      "answer": "Convoluted",
      "options": ["Assume", "Prevalent", "Convoluted", "Support"]
    },
    {
      "question": "There was a ______.",
      "answer": "Discrepancy",
      "options": ["Estimate", "Discrepancy", "Reluctant", "Alleviated"]
    },
    {
      "question": "It's ______ in business.",
      "answer": "Prevalent",
      "options": ["Prevalent", "Inevitable", "Maintain", "Ubiquitous"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The medicine _______ her pain.",
      "answer": "Alleviated",
      "options": ["Maintain", "Improve", "Articulates", "Alleviated"]
    },
    {
      "question": "He _______ well.",
      "answer": "Articulates",
      "options": ["Support", "Articulates", "Substantiate", "Determine"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Can you ______  that?",
      "answer": "Substantiate",
      "options": ["Maintain", "Substantiate", "Improve", "Reluctant"]
    },
    {
      "question": "She is ________ with her work.",
      "answer": "Meticulous",
      "options": ["Determine", "Meticulous", "Ubiquitous", "Improve"]
    },
    {
      "question": "She was _____ to speak in front of the class.",
      "answer": "Reluctant",
      "options": ["Reluctant", "Support", "Improve", "Inevitable"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Smartphones are _______ now.",
      "answer": "Ubiquitous",
      "options": ["Ubiquitous", "Improve", "Alleviated", "Prevalent"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Change is _______.",
      "answer": "Inevitable",
      "options": ["Reluctant", "Inevitable", "Maintain", "Substantiate"]
    }
  ]
  